There's a gentleman. You sleep with animals. You have the urge for animals.
Okay, come. Urge for animal.
As if you should get and abuse the animal anytime, anywhere.
So please come out. Jesus loves you.
I'm the young man you said that I have the urge for animals.
I used to see animals in my dream and I slept with them and after that...
Come here. See your mouth.
You mean, you sleep with animals?
Yes, Man of God.
Any animal that just shouts.
Your urge is so serious that when you hear (animal sound), you will grab them.
Yes, Man of God.
Man of God, deliver me, please!
How did you come about sleeping with your animals?
Man of God, I don't know.
Deliverance In Jesus' Name
Standard for Life
People of God, Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
Thank you very much.
My name is Wisdom Linus.
I come from Calabar, Nigeria.
The problem that brought me to The SCOAN was having the urge for animals.
The problem started last year, in August.
I'm a chef by profession; I cook for people at hotels or at their homes.
I was employed in Calabar, to cook for a lady.
In her compound there was a dog and I was the one who fed the dog;
after cooking, I would give the dog food.
One terrible night, I had a dream where I saw the dog with my picture.
Inside the dream, I beat the dog, saying, "What are you doing with my picture?"
From then, the following morning, I began to have affection for this dog,
as if it was my girlfriend.
All my human affection was dead; my feelings were for the dog alone.
When everybody had gone to bed, at the time I was supposed to release the dog
to do its duty, I would take the dog to my room when I was about to sleep.
Then, we would sleep together as boyfriend and girlfriend.
This had become a habit and because of the problem, I could not concentrate.
Sometimes, when the urge came after seeing the dog in the dream,
I would not be able to concentrate in the kitchen and I would make terrible mistakes.
I would put too much salt or flavouring and before I knew it, they sacked me.
The affection would happen like this:
when the dog would come in the dream, the next day,
everything around me would resemble the dog; I would see the dog every minute and every second -
both physically and spiritually.
That was how my focus was on the dog alone, not on human beings.
The feelings I had for the dog, were the feelings a person is supposed to have for a girlfriend.
For how long have you been having this problem?
Close to one year now.
Sometimes, I would realise that my affection was supposed to be for human beings, not for an animal;
when it came to my room because he would come to my door, I would chase the dog away.
After that, he would come and attack me in my dreams.
The following day, I would succumb to my feelings for the dog again.
I have prayed and visited several churches where I complained to many pastors;
they told me to fast and pray but my urge for animals continued.
Tell us, how did you receive your deliverance?
How did you get to know about Emmaneul TV?
The way I received my deliverance began through watching Emmanuel TV
because I love watching the channel so much
and seeing the way the man of God is delivering people;
evil spirits would manifest and speak about who they are.
I realized that it was my turn to be delivered because my urge was not normal.
I came last Sunday and to my greatest surprise, Prophet T.B. Joshua prophesied,
"There is a young man who has affection for animals".
I knew I was the one he was talking about, so, I came out.
The man of God stretched his hand towards me, and I fell.
From that moment, I do not have affection for animals any longer.
That night the man of God prayed for me, the dog attacked me in my dream.
The dog was carrying my picture, running up and down.
The next thing I saw was Prophet T.B. Joshua snatch the picture from the dog and that was the end.
When Prophet T.B. Joshua prayed for me, I saw fire coming out of my head
and I began to feel light, instantly.
Once again, let us put our hands together for our Lord Jesus Christ.
My advice to the whole world is this:
When you experience strange things in your life, don't take them for granted
and don't run from God; run to God.
He's the only one who can deliver you.
The SCOAN is a place to be, I've confirmed it. Praise the Lord!
We just want to advise, now that God Almighty has delivered you:
Nothing happens for nothing, and nothing comes by chance.
What happened to you, you know that definitely, it was caused by sin.
Now that God Almighty has delivered you, please make sure you give all your life for Christ,
accept Him with all your heart, make His Word the standard for your life
and we pray that God Almighty in His infinite Mercy will grant you the grace
to be far from sin, and be close to His Word, in Jesus' name.
Amen. Thank You, Jesus!
And we believe that the best is yet to come in your life, in Jesus' name.
Amen.
Once again, let us put our hands together for our Lord Jesus.
Thank You, Jesus!
Standard for Life
My name is Wisdom Linus. I come from Akwa Ibom, Nigeria.
The Lord has done a mighty thing in my life since last week, when I came here.
God Almighty used Prophet T.B. Joshua to save my life, by delivering me
from what I have passed through for the past eight years now.
I thank God; I'm so grateful because I really enjoy my stay at The SCOAN.
I give God all the glory, in Jesus' name.
A spirit was tormenting me for the past eight years; it was a spirit that gave me the urge for animals.
Since last Sunday, Prophet T.B. Joshua prophesied to me and delivered me,
I don't have such feelings anymore and I know that I am free, in Jesus' name.
I thank God that the Lord Jesus has visited me and my family and we are set free, in Jesus' name.
So what were you actually doing before coming down to the church?
I have not been working.
Sometimes, I asked people for help; other times, I washed cars in order to eat.
I had to struggle before I came here and received my deliverance.
Okay, so we've heard it from our brother, our brother was set free from an evil spirit
that pushed him to have an urge for animals.
Apart from pushing him into such a terrible act, it also destroyed his life,
especially his career as a chef and also his finances and everything connected to him.
But we give glory to God that he has been set free.
Since coming to The SCOAN, we've heard the wonderful testimony of the changes in his life.
So, brother, we are here today with a message from Prophet T.B. Joshua.
The man of God, Prophet T.B. Joshua, said that he wants to present to you a gift
on behalf of himself and Emmanuel TV partners worldwide
to really encourage you now to start a new life in Christ Jesus.
So we're here to present to you this gift of 200,000 Naira.
Mr Wisdom Receives Cash Gift Of 200,000 Naira
From T.B. Joshua & Emmanuel TV Partners
Wow, we can see the display of emotion from our brother.
Mr Wisdom Receives Cash Gift Of 200,000 Naira
From T.B. Joshua & Emmanuel TV Partners
I am so grateful; thank You, Jesus!
Mr Wisdom Receives Cash Gift Of 200,000 Naira
From T.B. Joshua & Emmanuel TV Partners
I thank God so much. I'm so grateful.
I know that my family has been set free.
With this gift, I'll come back with a great testimony. in the mighty name of Jesus.
I'm so grateful. I wasn't expecting this.
Thank you, Prophet T.B. Joshua, my mentor.
May God bless you, in the mighty name of Jesus.
I'm so grateful. Thank You, Jesus.
Hallelujah. We can all hear it from our brother.
That is the sum of 200,000 Naira for our brother.
On behalf of Prophet T.B. Joshua and Emmanuel TV partners,
we're also presenting to him the Word of God, 'The Mirror',
as a reminder for him to make the Word of God the standard for his life.
Do you believe, brother, that as you are going out now,
that you are going to make God's Word the standard for your life
and maintain this deliverance you've received?
Amen. Thank You, Jesus!
I thank God and I'm asking Him to give me the grace to maintain this deliverance
in order for me to help my siblings.
I will really work hard, to make sure this blessing will manifest very well
in my family and my life, in the mighty name of Jesus.
Amen. We thank God for your life,
and we pray that God will give you the grace to maintain all these wonderful blessings
you have received here at The SCOAN by making the Word of God the standard for your life.
We know the best is yet to come, in Jesus' name.
Amen. Thank You, Jesus.
RV: Mel Flowers 01/05/2019